[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["North Korea"]}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "What do you make of it all?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "it", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "Well, first of all, I think it is important that we focus at least some attention on North Korea.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "think", "it", "is", "important", "that", "we", "focus", "at", "least", "some", "attention", "on", "North", "Korea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["State Department"], "PERSON": ["Dan"]}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "Which has to in the end be the right way to go, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "has", "to", "in", "the", "end", "be", "the", "right", "way", "to", "go", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Well, I can hear in my mind's ear, people in the State Department scoffing and laughing and saying, listen, Dan and Piers don't know what they're talking about.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "can", "hear", "in", "my", "mind", "'s", "ear", ",", "people", "in", "the", "State", "Department", "scoffing", "and", "laughing", "and", "saying", ",", "listen", ",", "Dan", "and", "Piers", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "they", "'re", "talking", "about", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"]}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "CD", "WP", ":", "IN", "JJS", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "What did you make of it when you pored through it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "it", "when", "you", "pored", "through", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Well, I wasn't surprised because as one who -- at least once, I think twice received a handwritten note from then President Bush.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "was", "n't", "surprised", "because", "as", "one", "who", "--", "at", "least", "once", ",", "I", "think", "twice", "received", "a", "handwritten", "note", "from", "then", "President", "Bush", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Very quickly, what is it about?", "question_tokens": ["Very", "quickly", ",", "what", "is", "it", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "ATHER: Well, what it's about is the phenomenon of so many American seniors being preyed upon by international crooks, cowards, to take their money, with telemarketing and particularly with lotteries.", "answer_tokens": ["ATHER", ":", "Well", ",", "what", "it", "'s", "about", "is", "the", "phenomenon", "of", "so", "many", "American", "seniors", "being", "preyed", "upon", "by", "international", "crooks", ",", "cowards", ",", "to", "take", "their", "money", ",", "with", "telemarketing", "and", "particularly", "with", "lotteries", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "You have to wonder, are those mainstream fans going to want to sit down on their television sets on a Saturday night and watch this race called the NRA 500?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "to", "wonder", ",", "are", "those", "mainstream", "fans", "going", "to", "want", "to", "sit", "down", "on", "their", "television", "sets", "on", "a", "Saturday", "night", "and", "watch", "this", "race", "called", "the", "NRA", "500", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "JJR", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Saturday"], "ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"], "TIME": ["night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 317, "question": "Do you have a problem with this?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "problem", "with", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 318, "answer": "I don't have a problem with it, to tell you quite honestly.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "have", "a", "problem", "with", "it", ",", "to", "tell", "you", "quite", "honestly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "When you say backing away, you mean they may not support universal background checks?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "say", "backing", "away", ",", "you", "mean", "they", "may", "not", "support", "universal", "background", "checks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "Do we know what they paid the NRA?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "we", "know", "what", "they", "paid", "the", "NRA", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "We don't know their exact amount.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "do", "n't", "know", "their", "exact", "amount", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 378, "question": "What kind of message that this sends to their children that their favorite sporting event that they are going to see with the family maybe is sponsored by a gun lobby group?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "message", "that", "this", "sends", "to", "their", "children", "that", "their", "favorite", "sporting", "event", "that", "they", "are", "going", "to", "see", "with", "the", "family", "maybe", "is", "sponsored", "by", "a", "gun", "lobby", "group", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "You know, Piers, you're a fine fellow.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "Piers", ",", "you", "'re", "a", "fine", "fellow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NRA"]}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "RB", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "What are the repercussions and possible implications of Fox and the NRA in all of this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "the", "repercussions", "and", "possible", "implications", "of", "Fox", "and", "the", "NRA", "in", "all", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "Well, it's interesting, because the NRA has had so many controversial television ads lately, which we know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "interesting", ",", "because", "the", "NRA", "has", "had", "so", "many", "controversial", "television", "ads", "lately", ",", "which", "we", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Fox", "NRA"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "Yes, Senator Patrick?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "Senator", "Patrick", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "Just very quickly.", "answer_tokens": ["Just", "very", "quickly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Patrick"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "Is it also part of being an American to say, we have to find some way to keep irresponsible people from perpetrating these crimes, time after time, things like the Sandy Hook shooting?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "also", "part", "of", "being", "an", "American", "to", "say", ",", "we", "have", "to", "find", "some", "way", "to", "keep", "irresponsible", "people", "from", "perpetrating", "these", "crimes", ",", "time", "after", "time", ",", "things", "like", "the", "Sandy", "Hook", "shooting", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", ",", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "I agree.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "agree", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 524, "question": "How do they equate being a religious group with their appalling behavior, picketing funerals of soldiers, young children, the anti-gay outbursts and so on?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "they", "equate", "being", "a", "religious", "group", "with", "their", "appalling", "behavior", ",", "picketing", "funerals", "of", "soldiers", ",", "young", "children", ",", "the", "anti-gay", "outbursts", "and", "so", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 525, "answer": "They claim to speak for God.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "claim", "to", "speak", "for", "God", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Simple as that?", "question_tokens": ["Simple", "as", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 528, "question": "That's their all-encompassing excuse?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "their", "all-encompassing", "excuse", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 529, "answer": "I mean, it's not a good excuse at all but they do it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "a", "good", "excuse", "at", "all", "but", "they", "do", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "Do they brainwash people like you, young people?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "they", "brainwash", "people", "like", "you", ",", "young", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "Did they make you picket and do things that you now look back and find contemptible?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "they", "make", "you", "picket", "and", "do", "things", "that", "you", "now", "look", "back", "and", "find", "contemptible", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "How do you feel emotionally about losing all contact with your closest family because of this?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "emotionally", "about", "losing", "all", "contact", "with", "your", "closest", "family", "because", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "I mean, it was very traumatic when it first happened.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "it", "was", "very", "traumatic", "when", "it", "first", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 561, "question": "How many of them?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "of", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 562, "answer": "Three.", "answer_tokens": ["Three", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "How would you describe your religious conviction?", "question_tokens": ["How", "would", "you", "describe", "your", "religious", "conviction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "I wouldn't say any denomination specifically.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "say", "any", "denomination", "specifically", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "Is there anything Christian about the Westboro Baptist Church, in your view?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "there", "anything", "Christian", "about", "the", "Westboro", "Baptist", "Church", ",", "in", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "I thought that it was in the beginning.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "that", "it", "was", "in", "the", "beginning", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Westboro Baptist Church"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "It's interesting watching ex-presidential candidates, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "'s", "interesting", "watching", "ex-presidential", "candidates", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "It is kind of sad.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "kind", "of", "sad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 628, "question": "Does he have a point?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "have", "a", "point", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 629, "answer": "I don't see any great opportunity to do a deal.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "see", "any", "great", "opportunity", "to", "do", "a", "deal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", ",", "IN", "JJ", ",", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", ",", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "Would it have made any difference if Mitt Romney had been successful, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "it", "have", "made", "any", "difference", "if", "Mitt", "Romney", "had", "been", "successful", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "You can make the argument that -- it seems to me that, in general, Democrats have been a little more reasonable, a little bit more willing to compromise.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "can", "make", "the", "argument", "that", "--", "it", "seems", "to", "me", "that", ",", "in", "general", ",", "Democrats", "have", "been", "a", "little", "more", "reasonable", ",", "a", "little", "bit", "more", "willing", "to", "compromise", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "Is he the great unsung deal maker now on the international stage?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "the", "great", "unsung", "deal", "maker", "now", "on", "the", "international", "stage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "RISTOFF: I don't think the Obama administration is going to appoint him to be special negotiator for the North Korean matter.", "answer_tokens": ["RISTOFF", ":", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "the", "Obama", "administration", "is", "going", "to", "appoint", "him", "to", "be", "special", "negotiator", "for", "the", "North", "Korean", "matter", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["North Korea"]}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 648, "question": "Is this a bad thing?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "a", "bad", "thing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 649, "answer": "I think the notion of engaging North Korea is really a good thing.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "notion", "of", "engaging", "North", "Korea", "is", "really", "a", "good", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WDT", "VBD", "WDT", "."], "qSentId": 657, "question": "There is no hard evidence that Dennis knows which is which, is there?", "question_tokens": ["There", "is", "no", "hard", "evidence", "that", "Dennis", "knows", "which", "is", "which", ",", "is", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "WDT", "VBZ", "WDT", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 658, "answer": "In fact, he seemed to be a little confused about which was which.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "fact", ",", "he", "seemed", "to", "be", "a", "little", "confused", "about", "which", "was", "which", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dennis"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 667, "question": "Are these the right kind of moves that he should be making?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "these", "the", "right", "kind", "of", "moves", "that", "he", "should", "be", "making", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 668, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Harlem"]}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBN", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 675, "question": "Who knows?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "knows", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 676, "answer": "I like the 70 young people who gathered and did the Harlem Shake outside the Muslim Brotherhood headquarters.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "the", "70", "young", "people", "who", "gathered", "and", "did", "the", "Harlem", "Shake", "outside", "the", "Muslim", "Brotherhood", "headquarters", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130304pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "``", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "''", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 684, "question": "What's it all about?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "it", "all", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 685, "answer": "So we started out writing the book, \"Half The Sky,\" kind of the dead trees version, about the need to empower women around the world.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "we", "started", "out", "writing", "the", "book", ",", "``", "Half", "The", "Sky", ",", "''", "kind", "of", "the", "dead", "trees", "version", ",", "about", "the", "need", "to", "empower", "women", "around", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]